<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 15:43:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Netsoc Admin Part 1</title>
      <link>/building-netsoc-admin-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 15:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/building-netsoc-admin-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Building Netsoc Admin (#1) – Development Tools Introduction Last September we (UCC Netsoc) installed two servers and dedicated one of them specifically to servicing our members and their applications. It allows people to SSH in and run PHP, python and JS-based apps off each user’s subdomain. We wanted people to be able to manage their own info, databases and could access automated backups. After a month of looking at web panels and various solutions, it was apparent that what we wanted didn’t exist in a pre-built package unfortunately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Virtualised Development Environment</title>
      <link>/creating-a-virtualised-development-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/creating-a-virtualised-development-environment/</guid>
      <description>Creating A Virtualised Development Environment Vagrant and VirtualBox For our development environment, we’re going to want a way to easily simulate an ubuntu/linux server as well as an easy way to interact with it when we need to make changes. That’s where Vagrant and VirtualBox come in 😉
VirtualBox VirtualBox is a cross-platform virtualization application. It allows us to simulate having an operating system without having to use a physical computer for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IRC - Connecting to Intersocs</title>
      <link>/irc-connecting-to-intersocs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 16:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/irc-connecting-to-intersocs/</guid>
      <description>IRC – Connecting To #Intersocs User Accounts If you do not already have a user account for UCC Netsoc’s services, sign up at https://admin.netsoc.co/register
You will need a user account before continuing with this document.
Quickstart If this is your first time, please read the entirety of the document as we do not provide support as of yet.
 SSH into Leela with your user credentials: ssh USERNAME@leela.netsoc.co Access your Weechat IRC screen: irc /connect netsoc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>